Good morning. Good morning. You're
watching the program with Ted R and John
Kuryaku. John, good to see you.
>> Good to see you, Ted. Good morning.
>> Good morning. So, lots to talk about as
always. Um, so, uh, I love the there's a
couple of spy stories, so you might have
some stuff to say about this. the MSS,
[clears throat]
which is the CIA for uh China, is being
accused by the UK [laughter] of using of
recruiting assets or maybe agents
through uh LinkedIn. Yeah.
>> So, you know, I mean, this is good news.
I mean, for years I've been on LinkedIn
and I've never gotten so much as the
slightest lead from LinkedIn. So, I was
beginning to wonder if there were any
real jobs on it. So this indicates to me
that at least in the UK there are
[laughter] real jobs betraying your
country.
>> Let let me add something to that. So I'm
on LinkedIn all the time. I have
thousands and thousands of contacts. I
don't send out contact requests, but
people send them to me. I and unless
you're like obviously a nut or a weirdo
or a scammer, I just accept people. So
anyway, um about a year ago, I got a uh
I got a an invitation from a professor
in China at some university that I I
never heard of. And so I accepted it.
And then he said he he uh messaged me
and he said, "Oh, I've watched your
videos on YouTube and I would like to
invite you to come to China to speak."
>> Okay, [clears throat] great. I'd love to
go to China to speak. I have a speaker's
agent. I have a price.
And so, um, I said, "Great. Let's have
that conversation." In fact, that's
exactly what I said is, "Let's have that
conversation."
>> So, then he comes back and he says, "Um,
I've made all the arrangements for five
stops." And I said, "Whoa, wait a
minute. We haven't even begun to discuss
this yet.
>> So, no, we're not going to do five
stops. This has gone on for the last
year. And as recently as two weeks ago,
he emailed me and said, um,
why don't you respond to me? I've
already arranged all of your stops all
across Eastern China. And I wrote back
finally and I said, I don't do work for
the Chinese intelligence service.
And then he blocked me.
But that's what he was. I said I showed
I showed all these messages to a dear
friend of mine, Fultton Armstrong.
Folultton and I were at the CIA
together. He was the national
intelligence officer for for China. And
then we were on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee staff together. And
I said, "Tell me if I'm nuts, but this
is Chinese intelligence, right?" And he
looks at it and he says 100%.
>> The Ministry of State Security.
>> Yeah.
>> That's amazing.
>> I didn't expect there to be a personal
anecdote there. the the the Chinese the
the Chinese are successful when
when they're trying to recruit somebody
who just wants money. They don't care
about the fallout. They don't care about
the risks. They want money. The Chinese
have the money. In terms of developing a
source who may or may not realize he's
being recruited by Chinese intelligence,
they're really bad at it. They're
really, really bad at it. But normally
they're looking for people who have
access to very sophisticated technology.
>> Well, so in this particular case, I
guess we're just going to leap into it.
Uh just please like, follow, and share
the show. You know, all that stuff,
guys. Uh and we'll bring in Robbie later
on to talk about why you should all
watch us on LinkedIn on uh not on
LinkedIn. Well, maybe we'd make money on
LinkedIn working for China. Uh but uh
certainly over on Rumble. But okay, so
the allegation here from the UK and I
guess it's sounding increasingly
credible uh is that they approach
they've been approaching all sorts of
people like academics um MPs. What would
they want from a British MP? I mean I
guess some of them have access to
classified information. I mean, is the
idea basically like they dip their toe
in the water like come and work for us
and it sounds legit at first like you're
just asking for say a a white paper or a
report or something that's publicly
available and then and then you then
then you then they ask for something a
little more and it goes like that.
>> Normally that would be the the
progression. Yes. But with a member of
of parliament, you would all you would
also have access to inside information
on official deliberations.
Anything from trade to defense to
politics, you would have an insider
reporting back to you.
Now listen, 90% of the time you'll be
able to get that same information out of
a newspaper. But that extra 10%, they're
willing to pay good money for it.
>> Interesting. And money is no object.
>> Money's no object. They're they're flush
with money.
>> So whatever.
>> Um so I guess the question now is uh
what if uh what what if anything can the
UK or any target of this kind of
approach right
>> do to I mean obviously you can't
inoculate yourself but how can you
mitigate it [snorts and sighs]
>> right? Um, you know what? Teach your
people good counterintelligence
techniques. Most people wouldn't realize
that they were being pitched or targeted
by a Chinese intelligence officer. Um,
and that's the whole point from the
Chinese side. And so just, you know,
make sure
>> although they are Chinese people, the
head hunters here were clearly Chinese.
I mean, you know, someone named Amanda
Chu and Shirley Shen is clearly they're
clearly Chinese. But there's lots of The
problem is there's lots of legitimate
Exactly.
>> Chinese business people.
>> Exactly. Yes. So just have your counter
intelligence antenna up.
>> Yeah. And if there's something in your
gut that makes you think that that it's
wrong, something's wrong.
>> Too good to be true.
>> Yeah. Then then it is too good to be
true. Yes.
>> Yeah. Well, I would be suspicious, John,
of anybody approaching to offer me money
on LinkedIn. I'm really not kidding.
It's to me the most worthless thing
ever. Uh, I've never had anything legit
pop up ever. I mean, I've never had
someone say, "Hey, let's do a, you know,
would you draw a freelance cartoon for
me?" Or, "I'd like to just buy an
original." Nothing.
>> I I actually make money on uh on
LinkedIn. Really?
>> I I just made a thousand bucks a week
ago.
>> Good.
>> A guy asked me, he said, "Hey, can you
do a one-page paper for me?" I said,
"Yeah, give me a thousand bucks." And
boom, five minutes later, he sells it to
me. I've been f I must be I must
[laughter] well you might just have a
better profile than me but I also don't
I always wonder if I'm not doing uh
social media right. Uh all right well
other stuff to talk about. Um new poll
is out. Super interesting. Want to get
your thoughts about that about um it's
the first look at uh basically the
midterms and it looks like right now
Democrats would seem to be sitting
pretty but I'm not so sure I believe
that. Um, and then, uh, Trump has
authorized CIA covert action against
Venezuela. [sighs]
>> So, I want to talk to you about like
what that could possibly entail because
it seems like that's very broad and
possibly very vague.
>> And go ahead. And then last but not
least, I wanted to um I'm fascinated by
MK Ultra. My son is fascinating by
fascinated by MK Ultra. And you know,
this really seemed like something that
by now happened so long ago that it
would really be in our rearview mirror
and just a subject of history. Yeah.
>> But there's a new lawsuit um that's just
been authorized up in Canada in
Montreal. Uh there's a class action
lawsuit from one of the victims who was
she's quite old um but back in 1958
uh she was 16 years old. So, she was
born in 1942
and uh she went through all apparently
through all sorts of hell uh when she
was uh basically like kind of like a
disobedient juvenile delinquent type and
some judge, you know, basically sent her
off to the tender mercies of the MK
Ultra program that was being
administered by a Canadian guy who's now
long dead. Um,
>> and we know with 100% certainty that
many of the MK Ultra experiments took
place in Canada.
>> Why?
>> Um, we asked the Canadian Intelligence
Service to help us out. This was all
antis-siet, anti-Chinese, you know,
remote viewing and LSD and all that
stuff, and they gladly helped.
>> Was it just I mean, it was just because
we're we're just because we're allies.
Yeah. I mean, from the CIA point of
view, why not just do it here at home?
Or was it partly uh you know, it's a
little bit remote, it's a little bit
plausible, possible deniability?
>> We we mostly did it at home. What MK
Ultra is, for people who don't know, it
was a a top secret CIA program from
1955.
It the origins were 1952 up to 1975 when
they were caught by the Church
Committee. And so what they did was
things like they experimented on
American citizens without their
knowledge uh by dosing people with LSD.
Um they uh they hired prostitutes in San
Francisco to go out on the street, find
John's, lure them back to the CIA safe
house, and dose the John's with LSD just
to see if the John's would would give up
their deepest, darkest secrets. Uh they
they pumped a germ into the air during
an especially foggy uh morning in uh San
Francisco just to see if they could
successfully infect large numbers of
people and 11 people came down with this
very rare upper respiratory infection.
And then it was things like
>> same thing in the New York City subway
system. They dropped they dropped a germ
off the back of a subway in a light
bulb.
>> Correct. And it broke. And they wanted
to track it, right? It was about And
they thought it was innocuous. Yeah.
They thought and some really old guy who
suffered from us as uh who had it would
have been me. I I have respiratory
issues. Sure. And he was like, I don't
know, maybe 80 or something. And he
kicked.
>> He died.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. That's what they did. And there
were sub uh operations MK Chickwit, MK
Nightclub, um that that did other
things. The truth is the CIA dosed its
own employees with LSD. Um, at least one
committed suicide, probably two. And um,
and it was only because the the church
committee accidentally stumbled on it
that we know anything about it. And then
Senator Church in that hearing ordered
the CIA director to preserve every page
of documents. And he went back to CIA
headquarters and ordered everybody to
destroy everything. And so what we have
left is just about 20% of the documents
[snorts]
>> that they either hadn't found or didn't
destroy, couldn't destroy for whatever
reason. So we really don't know anymore
what MKLA
>> carbon paper carbon paper was an
investigator's friend back then because
every government memo was carboned,
right? Like you know for people who are
old, you know, is basically how to make
a Xerox copy before there was a Xerox
machine. And so, you know, like when
whenever I've researched government
archives, you'll often find the same
document, the same memo, uh, you know,
in six different archives because it
was, you know, different places. So,
it's hard for a government to get rid of
everything. It always looks like that.
>> Yes.
>> That last scene of Indiana Jones in the
giant arc in a giant warehouse.
>> Warehouse. Yeah. Um, somebody makes a
comment. Oh, no, no, we we'll get to
that. We'll get to that in a minute. But
anyway, MK Ultra, uh, I mean, and I I
know that I know that we've got a packed
show. We only have 45 minutes left and
there's a lot on the agenda, but I
wanted to say something, too. The
Washington Post is reporting today that
a Democratic
delegate, this is a non- voting member
of Congress from the US Virgin Islands
by the name of Stacy Plaset. I never
heard of Stacy Plasket until this
morning. She was found in these latest
Epstein documents to have been texting
Epstein in 2019 live while the Epstein
hearing was going on. Um, it was just
found in this in this trunch of
documents last night. a Republican from
South Carolina by the name of uh Ralph
Norman introduced a resolution to um
censure her, saying it was beyond
comprehension that she would communicate
with Epstein live during a hearing on
Epste.
>> Was this a closed door hearing?
>> No, it was No, but Epstein told her what
questions to ask of Michael Cohen,
Trump's former attorney.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah. Get this though. So he had his So
he had his uh he had his his eye in the
room.
>> Yeah, he [clears throat] did. He had his
eye in the room. The resolution to
censure her failed 214 to 209.
All Democrats voted no.
That just I mean talk about frigin
corruption.
>> That's disgusting.
>> Disgusting. Um, you know, by the way,
speaking of disgusting, uh, perhaps the,
uh, man in America with the dumbest
ideas about women in science, Larry
Summers. Yes. U, he, uh, you know, has
just stepped down right before the show
from the board of Open AI. I guess my
chances of of being, uh, decentered from
Jack GPT may have gone out the window
with him, or maybe not. Maybe they
they've increased, but uh, he's gone. Uh
he said he said that he was stepping he
he was not going to do this but a couple
of days ago he apologized said he was
deeply ashamed of his association with
Epstein and I assume more maybe than his
association
>> yeah so why didn't why didn't he say
that years ago
>> years ago
>> why now that we've caught him as a
pedophile
>> right
>> only now he decides he needs to resign
from these boards and only now is he so
deeply ashamed
>> and now he but he still wants to teach.
>> Yeah, he's going to teach and and he
still is going to teach unless Harvard
fires him. He's not the president of
Harvard anymore, but he's still a tenur
professor.
>> Absolutely unacceptable.
>> Yeah. And this is a I mean, by the way,
I don't know how much I would be
interested in learning from a person who
doesn't think that women are as good at
math and science as men. Call Marie
Kuri. Um, you know, [laughter] I don't
know. But, but I mean, so yeah, I mean,
he's been caught. I mean, is that it for
him? I mean, basically, it's this. This
is the new crisis management. When you
get caught doing something really
terrible, I'm gonna step aside. I'm
going to back off. I'm going to
reassess, spend time in therapy, maybe
go look at plants and animals. Um, you
know, I mean, and and so that's it. I
mean, the implication is really clear
that he he was doing very bad things to
very innocent girls.
>> Yes. Yes, he was indeed. Yeah. And
there's not going to be any price for
him to pay.
Just this self flagagillation that's all
for the public's consumption and then
that's all.
>> Um, question related to this for you,
John from De's Nuts.
I just watched your latest episode on
Deep Focus. You guys predicted that the
Senate would block the release of the
Epstein files, but last night the bill
passed. Thoughts?
>> Yes, I do have some thoughts. So, we
were wrong about that for for a reason
that developed very quickly. John Thun
had John Thoon, the Senate Majority
Leader, had said several times over the
past week that he was not going to allow
this thing to come to a vote. But night
before last, Donald Trump urged
Republicans to vote yes. They voted yes.
Well, it was the the final vote in the
House was 417 to one. Uh there was one
[snorts] just piece of trash from I
think it was from Texas that or
Louisiana that voted no and um and Thoon
realized that the the train had left the
station and it was barreling right
toward him and so he decided to to get
on the right side of this. But I'll tell
you what, and this is another indication
of the insider corruption that are both
parties. Um, to save Thoon,
Chuck Schumer asked for
>> [snorts]
>> um, a voice vote.
All those in favor say I. I. All those
opposed. The eyes have it. Just like
that. [clears throat]
That's literally
>> the length of time that it took.
>> Yes. They didn't They didn't do a roll
call.
>> No, there was no roll call vote. And so
there is no written record of how
anybody voted. And now literally
everybody but this clown from Louisiana
can say, "I stood up against the
pedophiles. I stood up against Epstein."
No,
>> Trump will sign. He will sign, right?
>> He said he'll sign.
>> Yeah.
>> Although today the Times has an article
saying, "Sure, he's going to sign it."
And then who's going to ensure that he
actually does it?
>> Right. Well, that's always the thing,
right? And like with the DO and of
course there's the get out of jail free
card. the DOJ saying, "Well, but there's
an ongoing investigation and we can't
release it just yet. We'll get back to
you." Um, John, thanks for the $5
donation. USX A-Rod is asking a very
pertinent question. Will there be any
way to tell if the release of the
documents is legit? I don't trust Bondi,
Patel, or Trump not to alter the
documents, especially after finally
agreeing to release them. I mean, it is
true that these are digital files and
you know, I I went I I did a deep but
it's common sense, but I did a deep dive
through this in my lawsuit against the
LA Times, which also involved like a
discussion of the difference between
analog and digital files. If a if you
have a paper memo like in the old days,
uh like carbon pop copied, it's very
easy to authenticate whether it's real
or not.
>> That's right. But a digital file is
really easy to manipulate. And it's very
almost impossible to authenticate. I
mean, the only way really you can
authenticate it, correct me if I'm
wrong, is by ver let's say, let's say,
for example, I email you and you and you
print it out and you say, "This is a
copy of Ted's email to me." And then you
can check with me and I can say, "This
is my copy of it." And if the two are
the same, then probably that's legit.
But that's not really beyond a
reasonable doubt. We both could have
altered it in the same exact or modified
it in the same way. I mean, if it's in
if it went to 10 different people, it's
far likelier that that's really the one,
right? I mean,
>> they can do what they did to Jesslyn
Raidak. Jesslyn Raak was one of my
attorneys in my case. She's a famous
whistleblower in her own right. She was
the director of ethics at the Justice
Department.
The night that John Walker Lind, the
American Talib, was was captured in
northern Afghanistan, the FBI called her
in the middle of the night and said, "We
we just
>> um we just caught an American citizen."
She said, "Whatever you do, you have to
read him his rights."
>> And they didn't.
>> I know. Well, she had written up a a
memo, an electronic memo, and it was in
the system. She sent a copy to the
attorney general, a copy to the head of
OLC, a copy to the head of this group
and that group.
>> How much for legal counsel?
>> Right. And so she goes into work and her
boss is like, "What are you doing? You
write a memo and you send it to
everybody in the building." She said,
"The guy has he's an American citizen.
He has constitutional rights." They
deleted that memo.
But she had printed a copy that they
didn't know about.
>> And she
>> that's the way
>> she sent it to a reporter at Newsweek.
Now the reporter at Newsweek then when
he published it as a a photo of the memo
forgot to redact her name.
>> Oh Jesus Christ. Is he working at the
Intercept now? This guy
>> might as well be. And so um she was not
just fired from her job as the director
of ethics. She was put on the nofly list
and the Justice Department tried to have
her bar license suspended.
So listen, the bottom line here is we're
going to just have to take their word
for it. Unless
>> Yeah, we are.
>> Unless they just screw something up and
a whistleblower comes forward.
>> Bobby saying pointing out something that
is true, but I don't think it makes a
difference. You said the metadata can be
an can be analyzed when you when you
alter it. It stamps the data. True, but
metadata can be can be falsified, too. I
mean, a really great example of that was
the the hack of the Hollywood studio
that was allegedly by North Korea and
that met and allegedly there was code in
there that was uh you know DPRK type
used hacker code, but anyone can cut and
paste that [__] in there. I mean,
there's
>> it's just digital. Digital information
is fungeible by definition. I mean all
of it even if it's you know the un even
if it's under the hood which is what the
metadata is right although metadata is
useful for investigations right that's
how they caught
>> um who remember the guy who um oh my god
that cyber guy who who went on the lamb
uh he he was a he had done a sec uh it's
it's killing me someone in the chat's
going to know this he was this very
flamboyant tech entrepreneur who did um
cyber security software and then he was
on the in the Caribbean and he was
sending photos to the authorities to
troll them and then the metadata from
like revealed where you know when you
send a photo when you take a photo with
your phone it tags where you are when
you take it. So anyway, the point is um
all right. So we have a bunch of
questions to get through here. Um
uh okay um Exile the Knights of Malta
now wants to know I have a question if I
haven't met if we haven't met the
threshold to require military tribunals
convened. What would that look like
then?
I don't know what that's about. Okay. Uh
sorry this one I'm gonna have to say I
don't know but I'm gonna look into frog
enthusiast. Ted, as a Frenchie, have you
been following the LFA cement company
prosecutions with relation to funding
groups in Syria? Whole thing stinks of
intelligence operations. I don't know
anything about this. I'll look into
this.
>> I don't neither.
>> Um, but I will look into it. Um, why
does Epstein never get compared to Bill
Browder, Mark Rich, uh, Kamoski of
Ukraine, etc. Is it because Epstein
didn't do business in Russia?
>> Wants to know.
>> That's a good question. Probably. And I
think we're so focused on the pedophilia
>> that people aren't really looking at the
at the influence operations that follow
the money at the same time. That's
right.
>> Um, this is for you, John. Head 877.
Did Israel actually threaten to nuke
Iran?
>> That's what President Trump said. We
don't we don't know if that's true, but
Trump Trump said just after we bombed
Iran that the reason he did it was that
Netanyahu told him, "If you don't bomb
Iran, we will and we're going to use a
nuke."
>> I believe Trump.
>> I I do too. I believe Trump on that.
>> I mean, it just it just you know how
sometimes it just rings something just
rings true. Mhm. Um, Frasmatas, uh,
Wikileaks DNC 2016 emails were
verifiable because the email server
generates a hash using an encryption key
or people use a PGP key to sign a
document. Um, okay. So, I got to I got
to push back on that on a number on on
two reasons. First of all, um, so my a
very good friend of mine was
instrumental in developing PGP pretty
good privacy. Um and he explained how
that works. And the point is it's not
100% for sure. Um the especially not now
it was kind of like you know cyber
security encryption is an arms race and
and things are always getting you know
you know what works stops working right
otherwise we'd still be using the enigma
machine. But the thing is the those de
those emails were not leaked by email.
Uh they were leaked on a thumb drive.
They were carried by a disgruntled DMC
staffer uh over to a park near American
University in Washington DC uh and
handed over to Craig Murray, former UK
ambassador to Usuzbekistan, who by the
way is the author of a couple of really
great books that I highly recommend.
>> Um and
>> he's a hilarious, brilliant guy who I
really hope to get to meet someday. and
uh he and anyway he uh he worked for
Wikileaks and basically and so we know
that the the thing that's tricky is
everybody's been inside those files,
right? Like so Russian intelligence has
been in there. I think Clovis has been
in there. everybody like broke in
because the DNC had shitty security, but
the people who actually handed it over
that was and we know because of the
speed of the that the data was sucked
out in is consistent with a thumb drive
as opposed to the much slower speed that
it would take to transmit over an
internet line. I mean, am I am I wrong
about that?
>> No, you're exactly right. And Bill
Benny, for those of you who don't know
who Bill Benny is, he is he he's the
former number four at NSA. His title was
director of technology, which says a
lot. Bill is one of the most brilliant
thinkers I've ever encountered in my
life and and a noted whistleblower in
his own right. And um
and Bill is 1,000% certain that
these documents were loaded onto a thumb
drive because he examined the the speed
at which the data was downloaded. And he
said that the speed indicates that it
could not possibly have been done
remotely, i.e. it wasn't the Russians
hacking into the DNC servers,
>> even though they did.
>> Yeah. even though they did on a
different issue.
>> They just looked.
>> Yeah, they looked. They didn't download
anything.
>> Um,
and then Bill asks, you know, another
question. If the if the DNC was so
surefire certain that these were
downloaded remotely, why would they not
permit the FBI to look at the servers?
>> Right?
>> They've never turned the servers over to
the FBI. So, what do they have to hide?
Well, you know, Hillary and her people,
she has this she has a heart on about
her servers.
>> Yes, she does.
>> Um, so yeah, so I I mean, I think
nothing like that is is really truly
verifiable. Um, so uh the term Epstein,
[clears throat] this is from podcast
Kiss Kid on YouTube, uh, sorry, on
Rumble. Um, the term fixer has been
applied to Epstein, but since he had his
hand in so many things, would Spy Master
be appropriate?
>> I don't know. What do you think, John?
That's your That's more you than me.
>> I don't know. I I I don't know to tell
you the truth.
>> I think he was a connector. Sort of like
a Malcolm Gladwell type, you know,
[clears throat]
connector guy. He just, you know, was
one of those people like for in this
case for evil. He connected people
>> and it kept him relevant in those
circles.
>> By the way, it's John McAfee. Uh thank
you very very much. Uh it's
for to Johnny Jackson for reminding us
of that. Yeah, McAfee was a wild man.
Um,
let's see. John, I heard some private
contractors, this is from Ry C2020, have
higher clearance than some agencies.
Could that be possible? Like for
employees of the Global Strategies
Group?
>> Yes, that is absolutely possible,
especially at places like DARPA, NSA,
and CIA. Uh, you know, it's funny. We
used to wear these badges. The badges
are color coordinated at the CIA. Now,
now they're standard across the entire
intelligence community. So, a blue badge
means top secret SITK gamma. Everybody's
got it. Everybody
>> if you're in the building.
>> If you're in the building. Um, and it
used to have an H on it. The H meant
SITK gamma.
Then there would be like,
>> what do those stand for?
>> Uh, special intelligence talent
compartment, keyhole compartment, gamma
compartment.
>> Okay,
>> that's everybody gets it if you're a CIA
employee. And then it goes up from
there.
>> It sounds so cool. [laughter] It's like
makes me want to join right now.
>> Um, green badges are contractor badges.
Yellow badges mean you're cleared only
to the secret level. So all of the um
most of the language instructors only
have yellow badges because they don't
need access to top secret information.
They're just there to teach a foreign
language. And then red badges means you
are not cleared. So the guy that works
in the Dunkin Donuts at the cafeteria,
he's got a red badge. And the lady that
vacuums the floor in the evening, she
has a red badge. But if you had if you
had compartments above top secret, like
the questioner is asking, they would add
letters to that blue badge. So you
wouldn't just have an H. You'd have an
H, an L, an E, a Q, an S, a T. And they
all meant something,
>> but then they did away with that.
>> So now if you're cleared
for something special, you know you're
cleared for something special and
everybody else in that compartment knows
you're cleared for something special. So
they're not going to advertise it on
your badge.
>> The badge is encoded.
>> That's right. The badge is encoded.
>> So yeah, it's not unusual at all. Like
for example, when I was the uh executive
assistant to the deputy director,
I had access to literally everything
that the directorate of operations was
doing around the world. So I had like
eight different compartments beyond SITK
Gamma. And then
there was this there was a guy
a man and a woman there. They were
colleagues, but they were really having
an affair and they made no effort at
hiding it. But anyway, um they would sit
in on my morning meetings, but they
belonged to the Directorate of Science
and Technology. And when I needed to
give them a briefing book or to go talk
to them or ask a question or whatever, I
had to go buzz their office, but I was
not allowed to step inside the office.
And it was because whatever they were
doing back there, it was too highly
classified for John to know about it.
>> Gotcha. Couple more questions, then I've
got to do an ad, do some uh
housekeeping. Um, village idiot, what
percentage of Congress do you think
legitimately could be credibly
prosecuted for a felony? Insider
trading, others? I'm going to say
probably 80.
>> Lots. Yeah, I I would have to agree.
lots.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, I'm I'm down on Congress
normally just cuz I have no respect for
them because I've I've worked with them
and they're mostly dogs.
But when
when something like this happens with,
you know, live texting Epstein during an
Epstein hearing
>> pig
>> happens. Yeah. And literally every
Democrat votes not to censure, the
entire party's corrupted.
>> Agreed with that. By the way, thanks for
the donations, Marble 455, thanks for
the two bucks. Who's the US's closest
friend? Canada or the UK? That's a good
question.
>> Uh yeah, the UK.
>> Mora, thanks for the two bucks.
>> That's an easy one.
>> Thank you for the two bucks. Um and uh
thank you for your support, you guys. Uh
we are in in dire need of cash these
days. You can say that again
>> for real.
>> Let me add one thing. We had a we had a
question right at the very beginning.
Um, somebody asked uh what's going on in
Greece. Kimberly Gilfoil's there and
they're loving on her.
>> While you're at it, John, someone's
asking about Greece building drones for
Ukraine. Is that a good idea? So, two
Greek stories. Go ahead.
>> So, I have I have family in Greece that
span the political spectrum.
My grandmother's first cousin was a
member of the Pullet Bureau of the
Communist Party of Greece. And on the
other side, I've got a a relatively
>> of my heart,
>> a relatively close cousin who was
elected governor of the Danese Islands
from the Conservative party. So, and
I've got everybody in between and they
all love Kimberly Gilfoil.
I don't understand it. But some of them
have told me that it's an extension of
>> Hold that thought because we're about to
lose an ad if I don't like read. Very
short. Looking for a comfortable but
unique option for your gaming setup?
Check out technosportusa.com
with a wide range of ergonomic chairs in
a array of colors. You'll definitely
make bring your setup to the next level.
Always comfy, never boring. Technosport.
Use code rumble for 10% off your entire
order. Sorry, John. As you were.
>> No, no worries. No worries. Um,
yeah. So, they love Trump in Greece. I
don't know why, but they love Trump. And
I think that this love of Kimberly
Gilfoil is an extension of their love
for Trump.
>> Um, all right. So, a little more
housekeeping. Bringing in Robbie to
remind people who are new to the show
and maybe people who just are stubborn
uh why they need to watch us on Rumble.
Robbie.
>> Uh, hi. Fuzzy Robbiey's here, but
apparently he's going to be clear thanks
to one of our uh one of our fans is
going to generously has offered to buy
him a new camera. So, thank you if
you're watching.
>> Thank you. y'all will be able to see me
in all of my shinyheaded, non-fuzzy
glory [laughter] once that happens. Uh,
but no, the reason why we are why we're
on Rumble, well, it's it's twofold. One,
and most pertinent to John and Ted, is
that it pays significantly better for
every nickel that YouTube pays at ads
because they're in the Rumble creator
program, Rumble pays about 90 cents per
dollar. So, if you watch on Rumble, they
get paid more and because they have
bills, they appreciate getting paid
more. So, watch us on Rumble and it
really does help a ton. Second, Rumble
is a free speech platform. They put out
content on Rumble that you cannot see
anywhere else. And if you are a a
channel subscriber for $5 a month on
Rumble, you have access to all of that
to uh all of that content. Plus, unlike
YouTube, Rumble sends 100% of that money
to the show. They don't take a cut out
of it at all. YouTube takes about 35 to
40%. Rumble gives every dime of it to
the show hosts. So if you all want this
to continue, follow us on Rumble. See
content you you don't get anywhere else
and stand for free speech.
>> All right. Thank you very much for that,
Robbie. Okay, so we have we can do more.
We should do more. Let's bang out the
questions and then we need to get to our
remaining stories. Um
>> uh real quick, uh Greek drones to
Ukraine. I didn't um you know for for me
personally I think I think it's I don't
know it's a good idea if you're Ukraine
and Greece because the Greeks have this
nent defense contracting industry and
it's going to be good for the economy
but you know just I don't know prolongs
the war I suppose.
>> Yeah it does. I mean we know the inev I
think the inevit uh you know it's the
conclusion here is inevitable although
it's been grindingly slow. Uh, Village
Idiot also wants to know, have we
covered Seth Rich or the J6 Democratic
HQ pipe bomb? Not really.
>> No, we really haven't.
And and I'm wondering if that article in
the Blaze was incorrect. You know, they
said they said that the pipe bomber was
this uh female Capitol police officer.
>> Nothing came of that.
>> Who had been on rotation to the CIA. She
finally came out through her attorney
and said, "That is a bald-faced lie."
and I never had anything to do with
anything and then it just kind of went
solid.
>> She should sue. That's that's the proper
solution here because when you sue you I
mean it's like when you're defamed or
lie as I learned um you have to you have
to sue because then you're telling the
world I'm willing to spend money and
time to to stand up for my good name and
I'm going to expose myself because
there's going to be discovery. So if I'm
lying it's going to I'm I'm putting up
or shutting up, right? Everyone's going
to find out the truth. Um, thanks for
the buck. Uh, Junah A. Javeed, this is
for you, John. Pakistan's new field
marshall. Seems like he's making moves.
Imran Khan is in jail. Corruption is
high. Corruption's always high. It's
Pakistan. Pakistani US relations are
quote unquote improved. Thoughts?
>> You know, I turned down another
interview this morning from CNN India
and they were like mad. This time they
sent five questions. They were like,
"Answer our questions." And I said, "You
guys, what part of no do you not
understand?" I said, "Every time I
answer a question about Pakistan or
India, you guys make it a banner
headline with three exclamation points.
You take it completely out of context
and then I get a dozen death threats."
No need.
>> So, the answer is no. But I will say
this, and I'll probably get threats for
this, too.
>> Pakistani
corruption is so deep and so broad. Um
>> that's totally true
>> that it's almost impossible for the
country to have a true functioning
democracy. Pakistan also has a long
history of military coups and other
interventions into its democracy. Um
Iran Khan should not be in prison.
>> It's really it's not really a democracy.
It's really it's really a military
dictatorship with a veneer of democracy.
>> That's right. But Iran Khan shouldn't be
in prison. He should be allowed to uh
you know defend himself and uh and have
his day in.
>> They always knock they always send their
former prime ministers to prison.
>> Every one of them.
>> Nawas Sharif.
>> Every last one of them. Benazir Bhau.
>> Mhm. Yes.
>> It's like it's like that's you know that
like when you run for the job. Well, I
will end up in prison at some point.
>> I don't know who would want the job.
>> God. Or you get assassinated.
>> Or you get assassinated.
>> Um thanks for Angela Fala. Much
appreciated.
So Q clearance for energy or for
financial?
>> Ah Q is for energy and um it's
temporary. So Q clearances are
controlled by the department of energy.
I only had a Q clearance once. I had to
go to uh to Tennessee for a conference
and so they gave me a Q clearance that
lasted only for the duration of the
conference and then they took their Q
clearance back. But Q really is it's a
clearance for nuclear information.
>> [snorts]
>> Um,
>> so they jealously guard it.
>> Okay, off-topic question from Peruse.
Um, how easy is it to spoof the AIS
signal on yachts and ships, i.e. make
them disappear when they sail and
pretend they're somewhere else? I
understand this is possible.
>> I have no idea.
>> Uh, it sounds sounds like something that
would be pretty easy to do though um to
me. Um, Fu said, "Thanks for the buck."
He said that he served in the Peace
Corps in Palao and and Micronisia. Have
you ever been to any of the South
Pacific Island?
>> No, but I'm dying to go. But I'm gonna
go to the Solomon Islands in July with
Jeremy Kismarov of Covert Action
Magazine and we are going to do some
live on the ground reporting on this
kurfuffle between the United States and
China over who should have access to
Japan's World War II era um military
bases. So, we're going to we're going to
get there through Fiji, which I've also
never been to. And um and we're gonna
spend about 10 days on Guad Canal. I'm
excited about it.
>> Well, it sounds amazing. Everyone I know
who's been to places like Tahiti or the
Micronesian island of Yap um has
absolutely loved it. Even though it
takes 50 million years and 16 flights to
get there. Uh but you know, but at least
with the air traffic controllers back to
work and not calling it sick anymore. I
just want to parathetically say these
air traffic controllers kind of are
irritating me. Like they it's like you
were in the middle of a shutdown and it
was treated as legitimate by everybody
that they're kind of like slow walking
and calling in sick and it's kind of
like oh well you know you can't blame
them. I'm sorry. Like you're going to be
paid later. You get paid much more than
the average American gets paid for
whatever they're doing. Y like and
you're doing an important like really
important job and it sucks that you're
not being paid. you should be paid, but
[snorts] be a patriot and show up to
work and and you know and tell the
planes where to land. I'm sorry. It
annoys me. It's like or let's treat
everybody who who withholds their labor
with the same level of respect and
consideration and say like, oh, you
know, you're not paid enough and you
want to slow walk or do a sick out, then
good for you. But like it's just because
you're an, you know, somehow they have
special papal dispensation for being
ATC, which I guess they didn't have
under Reagan. Uh I don't know. It's It
annoys me.
>> Yes.
>> Okay, let's talk about uh what what
should we talk about? Venezuela. Um
should we talk about
>> Yeah, let's talk about Venezuela. And
may I start off by by by saying
something about covert action. So the
president announced this covert action
program against Venezuela, presumably to
overthrow the Maduro government.
>> Let me tell you how unusual it is for a
president to even utter the words covert
action.
I I was a witness in the Scooter Libby
trial in 2006 or 2007, I guess it was,
and I had to go before the special
prosecutor who ironically prosecuted me
a couple of years later. So, I I'm I'm
meeting with the special prosecutor and
the CIA general counsel's office is
represented and Scooter Liby's attorneys
are there and the Justice Department has
its people there and um
and he asked me a question.
Did I ever see these two senior CIA
people talking to each other? And I
said, well, they're not friends, if
that's what you're getting at. I mean,
the only conversation I ever saw them
have was about a covert oper a covert
action program. And the CIA general
counsel jumps up and he's like, "Stop."
And I said, "I wasn't going to say
anything about covert action." He's
like, "You can't even say the words
covert action. We don't even acknowledge
that there is such a thing as covert
action."
And I said, "Okay, sorry."
>> Now the president's going on television.
Yeah, he's going on national television
uh to talk about the covert action
program that he just approved at, you
know, six levels above top secret.
>> Boogs Fano of GG is calling me out. Can
you be any more anti-worker? Telling
people to suck it up when they're not
getting paid is crazy. No, I'm saying
that if anybody quits for not being
paid, they should be treated with that
respect. I don't like the fact that
there's an exception for air traffic
controllers that somehow when they do
it, it's okay. But when the rest of us
don't do it, it's not okay. So, I'm
doing what aboutism. Sorry. [laughter]
That's that's right.
>> That's my thing. Yeah. Right.
>> There's a lot I'm I can defend what
aboutism. Um, okay. So, covert action
can take many many forms. I mean, I
think of some really notorious examples
during the Soviet Union when American
commandos blew up the Trans Siberia oil
pipeline in Siberia, causing ecological
damage. Uh when the US hired um Afghan
uh gerillas, terrorists to cross the
Amudaria River and then uh attack a an
oil refinery in uh what was then the
southern USSR. Um, but it can also be
like dumping cash in a bathroom in
Moscow. So, to try to undermine the
state currency, the ruble. Um, there's
all sorts of things you can do. Um, so
when covert action is authorized by the
president of the United States, um,
first of all, does it does it HAVE TO BE
AUTHORIZED or does the US just does the
CIA just do covert action as a matter of
course? And then if it has to be
authorized, does it have to be specified
like, well, you can you can blow up, you
know, energy infrastructure, but you
can't do a cyber attack or you can do a
psychological operation, but you can't
do this. How does it work? [snorts]
>> It's very bureaucratic. So, the CIA has
something called the covert action
staff.
And let's say I have an idea. Hey, I
have an idea to overthrow the Venezuelan
government. I write it up and I take it
over to the covert action staff. They
put it in the proper official format and
then they send it to the um operational
component that would have jurisdiction
over it. If they say, "Yeah, this is a
good idea. Let's overthrow the
Venezuelan government." Then they send
it up the chain to the deputy director
for operations. If he signs off on it
and the director signs off on it, then
it goes to the general counsel. The
general counsel has to decide that it's
legal to overthrow the Venezuelan
government. If he decides it's legal,
then it goes to the Office of Legal
Counsel at the Department of Justice. If
they decide it's legal, then it goes to
the National Security Adviser. I'm
sorry, to the National Security Council
General Council. If he decides it's
legal, it goes to the national security
adviser for a signature. If that
signature is forthcoming, it goes to the
president. If the president signs it,
then the CIA can go ahead and try to
overthrow the Venezuelan government.
>> That's kind of insane. Um, before we
take some more questions, uh, I do have
to I do have to point out, so the
government went to the Trump
administration went to war against
Antifa, which is an organization that
doesn't actually exist as an
organization. Now, uh, they are going to
they're going to war against the
so-called cartel de los Solless.
>> Oh my god, I read this.
>> This is such a great story. Right. So,
the cartel, it sounds like a, you know,
like as an American, I was like, okay,
well, that sounds like a a real evil
cartel thing that we should maybe be
doing something about. As it turns out,
there's no such thing. So, it's just a
term that Venezuelan journalists came up
with and became popular among
Venezuelans
uh to describe um stars. Soles is stars
in in in Spanish and it means cartel of
the stars. And what it is, it's an
insult to refer to the generals who are
corrupted by drugs in Venezuela,
cocaine, and they have lots of stars on
their uniforms. So, it's basically
saying that these are drugcorrupted, but
they don't have a cartel. It's kind of
like just it's an expression. It's not
real. And yet, this is now on an
executive order. It's an internal
document. the Secretary of State talking
about this threat presented by the
cartel de Solis counting on the
ignorance of the American people. John,
does Trump and Marco Rubio, do you think
they know that it's [__] and they
just don't care or do you think they
don't really know it's [__]
>> I think they know. I think they know and
they don't care. You know, one thing
about Trump is when he decides he wants
to do something, he's not going to let
anybody stand in his way,
>> whether what he wants to do is legal or
illegal. And so,
>> is he really that different from other
>> He's the same as every other president.
The only difference is that he actually
says it out loud.
>> Yeah, I like that part, actually.
>> Yeah, I do. I do. You got to respect it.
>> Yeah, I do. Um, question for you. Uh,
John, are you uh Well, I'm going to skip
this. Um Oh, well, okay, John, quickly.
Are you Are you familiar with the great
community in Tarpon Springs, Florida,
and the sponge docks downtown?
>> Oh, yes, yes, yes. Uh Tarpon, man, is
one of my favorite places. It's um the
the Greek food is absolutely incredible.
Um they're all from the island of of
Galimnos down there, which is the next
island north of where my my family is
from, but Tarpon has been a a mecca for
for Greek um immigrants for a century.
And u it's because so many people in in
Calimnos were uh sponge divers. And it's
the same it's the same situation in
tarpon where you can dive for sponges
and they did a 100red years ago. So
yeah, I love tarpon.
>> Thanks very much for the generous $20
donation from MT16N7.
Did we see the story about the UK
Ministry of Defense putting warning
stickers inside its Chinese-made staff
cars advising staff not to discuss
classified [laughter]
information due to fears of built-in
microphones. Oh, and it's in all the
papers, the Telegraph, the Times, the
Guardian, the Daily Mail, the UK Defense
Journal. Oh my god. Yeah. What What in
blazes would possess them to buy Chinese
cars for the UK
Defense Ministry leadership?
>> Oh my god.
>> Well, I guess they couldn't afford
Rolls-Royces, right? Um, Finnish Finnish
Leica just says, "Thank I find it
astonishing. I can actually communicate
and my stupid messages are read by
people of stature here. There's so many
great intellectual people around social
media, academics, scholars. I know I
find that amazing. Uh, American pastime
for you, John. Generic question. How did
you decide on what counted as truth in a
world based on secrecy while at the
agency? And unfortunately, we don't have
two hours to answer this. Also, did your
understanding of the truth change after
you left?
>> No. No. I I say this all the time.
In our guts, we all know the difference
between right and wrong, truth and
fiction. And um you you just can't let
that culture, that culture of secrecy
bastardize what you know to be the
truth. And so you just have to, you
know, trust in yourself, trust in your
judgment, and know deep down that you
always have to do the right thing
>> because the truth's going to come out
and you on the right side of it. It
always does.
>> Last but not least, we really do have to
talk about this. So, uh, the new NPR PBS
Merist poll shows Democrats ahead by a
lot in a generic congressional race by
55% to 41%. Independents are plus 33 for
the Democrats. This looks a lot like
2017 before what turned out to be a a
big blue wave uh in Donald Trump's first
term midterm elections in 2018. Um so
Trump's approval is really low even for
him. Historically, he's always uh sort
of weaved between 40 and 45. Sort of
average 42. Currently at 39, but he's
got very strong disapproval. That's
stronger than usual. He's get
Republicans are being blamed for the
shutdown. Although I think everyone
Well, there's going to be more
shutdowns, right? We're only good till
January.
>> Yeah, we're only good till January.
>> Um 57 So, here's the thing, John. 57% of
Americans say that they want prices to
drop more than they care about any other
issue. They just don't care. John is
isn't the media and everyone getting
everything wrong? Nobody Prices aren't
going to drop. Can't drop. And we don't
want them to drop because that would be
deflation. Right.
>> Right. I mean, what we need, don't we?
What we don't what Americans really need
is higher incomes?
>> Oh, absolutely. But I think they're not
thinking about higher incomes. They they
want prices to go back to what they were
a year ago or two years ago.
>> It's not going to happen.
>> It's It's not going to happen. You know,
I I'll I'll admit to everybody, and I'm
not proud to admit it, but I really like
raviolis. Like just right out of the
can. I don't even heat them up. I just
open the can and eat them out of
[laughter] the can.
And I don't know why, but I just I have
this thing where I refuse to pay more
than 99 cents for a can of raviolis. And
so I'll just wait until they're on sale
for 99 cents. They're usually a buck and
a quarter. So
I went to the grocery store the other
day and the the raviolis are $2.49.
>> Whoa.
>> $2.49 for a can of lousy raviolis. I'm
not going to do it. I'm not going to I'm
not going to pay it. I won't spend the
money. I want I want everything to come
down to where it was a year ago, too.
>> Me, too. But I I mean, I just think But
the I mean, I'm gonna I'm going to write
about this very soon, maybe next week,
just about I mean, really truly for both
parties,
>> the solution here has to be
>> um you know, higher higher income,
higher wages. I mean, that's what's been
screwing the American people is higher
prices are not a solvable problem
because of the way that the system is
currently set up. Um, okay. So, cartel
de lo solus. Well, I mean, I guess. So,
what so what do you think? I mean, what
kind of um
>> covert actions are we going to actually
do in Venezuela?
>> Um, you know, [clears throat] probably
lots and lots of propaganda. That's the
easiest sort of entrylevel covert
action. Lots of propaganda. And I
wouldn't be surprised if we uh
eventually begin arming opponents of uh
President Maduro.
>> Wow. that would really ratchet things up
and then then you're going to have
fighting in the streets.
>> Maduro has uh reportedly offered to
resign in two years in exchange for the
US having access to Venezuelan uh having
I guess concessions for Venezuelan uh
oil and natural gas. Um the apparently
Trump said no to that. Why would we say
no?
[sighs] Not that we don't have access to
this either. I don't understand that. I
mean, oil is a global energy is a global
market. I mean, we don't really care
about specific Venezuelan oil. We just,
you know, we just want more oil so the
prices go down so that our cost the
costs for industry go down. But anyway,
that aside, we have like a minute.
>> Yeah. I I
I don't know. We we used to buy almost
all of Venezuela's oil anyway and it
would be refined in Texas and it put
people to work and
>> it gave us free not free it gave us
cheap oil and then we cut them off.
>> That's it.
>> So maybe
>> that's very strange, right? Like we're
cutting It's just like the way that we
and the Europeans cut off uh Russian oil
and gas.
>> Yes.
>> It's like why would we do that? It's
like we're cutting off our own nose
despite our face. It's not like
Venezuela and and Russia can't sell
their [__] elsewhere. Anyway, thanks
everyone for tuning in. We're going to
be back tomorrow, Thursday at 9:00 a.m.
as we are uh every Monday through
Friday, 9:00 a.m. And uh so uh thank
thanks for listening and uh please like,
follow, and share the show as Robbie
Counled. Please kindly watch us over on
Rumble. It makes a huge difference.
Thanks for all your generous donations.
Please stay tuned for the TMI show with
Ted R and Manila Chan. That's me, Ted R.
And uh we're on in just a minute. See
you later. Bye, John. Bye-bye, Ted.
[music]
>> [music]